{
    "subject": "resource/Margo_Humphrey",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Oakland,_California",
    "human_readable": "Margo Humphrey was born in Oakland, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9240092635154724,
            "question": "Where was Margo Humphrey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.825657844543457,
            "question": "Where else was Margo Humphrey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201897740364075,
            "question": "When was Margo Humphrey born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5684413909912109,
            "question": "What state is Oakland, California in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4791965186595917,
            "question": "Is Margo Humphrey from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41233396530151367,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Margo Humphrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2847641110420227,
            "question": "What is Oakland known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26069870591163635,
            "question": "Is there anything interesting about the name Margo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2576645016670227,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Oakland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24661658704280853,
            "question": "Does the name Margo Humphrey ring a bell?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Margo Humphrey was born in Oakland, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8357_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Oakland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8357_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything interesting about the name Margo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8357_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Oakland known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8357_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8357_3.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. All five documents mention Margo Humphrey being born in Oakland, California, and one document even specifies the year of birth as 1942."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Margo Humphrey's birthplace as Oakland, California. Therefore, the statement \"Margo Humphrey was born in Oakland, California\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}